

CONTACT ME

EYLINBXY@GMAIL.COM

8686 4989

www.linkedin.com/in/eylin-booi

SKILLS SUMMARY

- •••• HTML/CSS
- •••• Javascript, Java, Node.js
- •••• PHP, MySQL, jQuery
- •••• AJAX, JSON
- •••• Android Studio
- •••• ReactJS, Java Springboot
- •••• ASP.NET MVC, C#
- •••• Project Management
- •••• Communication Skills
- •••• Problem-Solving Skills
- • • Customer Service
- ••• Bilingual (English, Mandarin)

EYLIN BOOI XIN YU

PERSONAL PROFILE

A highly motivated professional with prior cabin crew experience, possessing strong interpersonal and communication skills. I am committed to utilizing my diverse skill set and passion for creating exceptional user experiences to contribute to innovative software projects.

WORK EXPERIENCE

ST ENGINEERING, SOFTWARE ENGINEER

MAR 2023 - CURRENT

 Collaborate with other developers and engineers to complete project through full-stack development

SCOOT, CABIN CREW

NOV 2017 - OCT 2020

- Conducting pre-flight check to ensure safety equipment is functional
- Ensure passenger's compliance to safety regulations before take-off and landing
- Resolve passenger's complaints on flights and doing service recovery upon receiving complaint on board
- Managing passenger conflicts on flight to maintain safety
- Performing first-aid on passengers while keeping a calm composure
- Working closely together with colleagues to provide topnotch experience for passengers

KANTAR MILLWARD BROWN, PROJECT MANAGEMENT INTERN

MAR 2016 - AUGUST 2016

- Liaising with suppliers and client service team
- Drafting timeline for complex multi-country projects
- Ensuring quality control of every project
- Monitoring to ensure project datelines are met

EDUCATIONAL HISTORY

MURDOCH UNIVERSITY

Bachelor of Information Technology in Mobile and Web Application Development | 2021 - 2023

REPUBLIC POLYTECHNIC

Diploma in Consumer Behaviour and Research | 2014 - 2017